H019
父の日記帳
H019  •  動名詞の発展用法
Deep in the drawer of my father's desk, I discovered
an old diary.
He seems to have been writing for a long time.
I hesitated to open it.
For a moment I held my breath.
Reading it would mean entering the private world of
my father's heart.
But I could not avoid the temptation.
I picked it up and began reading each line.
In his youth, my father had been composing poetry.
In every word, there was a joy in life, but also a small
regret at the bottom of his chest.
My father is always quiet and says little.
But inside that diary, another father existed.
I quietly returned the diary and closed the drawer.
Glimpsing my father's past filled me with a new
respect for him.